Vicki Deinhamer

6975 SW Vermont Ave Portland OR 97223 Cell (503) 819-8176 Email: paralleloperations@yahoo.com

Goal

Full-time employment in a dynamic, energetic, friendly and customer-service based environment.

Proficiencies:

Possess a strong history of successful Customer Service activities and skills. Self-starter. Love to work with people to provide them with personal and professional interaction and service. Employ use of probing questions that facilitates ability to think, create and respond creatively and quickly, with courtesy and empathy. 3-year member of Toastmasters; winner of Montana's 1985 State Toastmaster's Extemporaneous Speech Contest. Chosen by College President to testify against elimination of educational budget cuts before Montana's 1985 Legislature.

Education

1982-1987 Honors Communications BA, Eastern Montana College.

Experience

Technology-Based Call Center Customer Service, ACS (a Xerox Corporation), Tualatin OR, Dec 2010-Present Agent for information-intensive call center position that supports Apple's iPhone. Strong customer service articulation and listening skills facilitates successful interaction and assistance with a variety of personalities and individuals who call with issues related to their iPhones. Required to pinpoint and resolve efficiently, skillfully and professionally customer issues. Agent performance is monitored in part by customer survey feedback submitted to Apple.

Part-Time Retail Sales Associate, Lemontree Gift Shop, Portland OR, Oct 2008-Present

Work without supervision in a smaller gift shop in a higher-end neighborhood. Responsible for friendliness, daily sales generation and outstanding customer service to owner's customers who are loyal customers and visit regularly. Manage deliveries, unpack inventory and perform invoice justification. Balance register at end of day when owner is out of town. Keep store tidy, clean and organized. Assist with creatively updating store displays. Created and implemented 2010 store inventory system.

Part-Time Personal Assistant. Portland OR. April 2010-Oct 2010

Performed myriad of personal and professional and personal tasks and duties: scheduled appointments, maintained professional social networking sites; drafted business letters; conducted business invitation phone calls; managed personal and business expenses; created and implemented personal file system.

Independent Contractor, Agora Ventures LLC, Portland OR, March 2003-Jan 2009

Initiated and coordinated buyer and seller commodity pre-sales transactions. Position required high domestic and international phone volume with precise, knowledgeable and personable phone interaction for development of worldwide business relationships. Vetted buyers and sellers.

Customer Website Coordinator, Intel, Hillsboro OR, March 2002-Feb 2003

Solely responsible for maintenance and editing of Intel's 500+ customer based product website through proprietary Intel-based software. Performed extensive data and spreadsheet management on a daily basis. Left this 1-year temporary position one month early to pursue opportunity as independent contractor (above).

Senior Customer Service Rep, NEC Electronics, Portland OR, October 1994-Jan 2001

Sr. Customer Service Rep coordinator for HP Printer Division, of which HP was 1 of the top 10 NEC focus customers. Position required pro-active, personable and accurate communication and interaction with customer to handle all inside sales activities from order placement through to successful delivery to HP customer.